We've got a lot of sand to move out of here
我们得把大量的沙子搬离这里
if we gonna build this castle.
如果我们要搭这座城堡的话
It's a good thing I brought my robot,
幸运的是我把我的机器人带来了
just tell him what to do, Franklin.
只要告诉他做什么  富兰克林
Robot, shovel up the sand.
机器人  把这沙子铲一下
Shovel sand, shovel sand.
铲沙子   铲沙子
Now we need water...
现在我们需要水
robot, pour that bucket of water right here.
机器人  把那桶水倒在这里
Pour water, pour water.
倒水  倒水
Good job, robot, I wish he was a real robot.
干得好  机器人  我希望他是一个真正的机器人
Yeah, then we can make a sand castle as big as a real castle.
是的  那样子我们就能造一个像一个真的城堡的那样大的沙堆城堡
Forget the sand castles,
先不说沙堆城堡
I'll tell it to clean up my room.
我会叫它帮我打扫房间
Good idea.
好主意